Parham Javadi

Irvine, CA • pjfooeve09@yahoo.com • 310-923-8803 • linkedin.com/in/parham-javadi

Portfolio: https://pjfooeve09.github.io/

Full stack software engineer looking to advance my career in software development. Health Informatics graduate student with 4 months of experience as a software engineer intern and 2 years of experience in Health IT. Familiar with multiple EHR systems and skilled in web development.

SKILLS

Programming/Technical

Ruby on Rails, JavaScript, Vue.js, MySQL, HTML, CSS, GitHub, Jenkins, SPSS, EPIC, WordPress, Microsoft Office (advanced Excel, PowerPoint, Word)

EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer Intern, Bamboo Health - Remote

January 2022 - May 2022

Bamboo Health (formerly Appriss Health + PatientPing) is a healthcare tech solutions company, focused on cultivating care collaboration.

- Assisted in software development and debugging
- Wrote unit tests to streamline and assist quality engineers in completing regression and reduce hotfixes
- Installed, configured, and troubleshooted test environment
- Participated in Agile Software Development team
- Used JIRA to create and keep track of tasks and sub-tasks assigned in the sprint

Medical Records Field Technician, Ciox Health – Los Angeles, CA

May 2019 – Dec 2021

Ciox Health helps clients (hospitals, clinics, etc.) manage, protect, and leverage health information to achieve operational improvements, optimized revenue, and better patient outcomes

- Traveled to client sites to scan and retrieve medical records and patient charts for audit and ensure all necessary charts are collected in a timely manner (~15 charts per hour).
- Reviewed charts and flag incomplete or inaccurate information.
- Maintained accuracy, completeness and security for medical records and health information.
- Communicated with the site's IT department to resolve technical issues.
- Worked with various EHR systems including NexGen, Prime Clinical Systems, MD Suite, Allscripts, UroChart, Eye MD EMR Optometry, eClinicalWorks, Intergy EHR, Practice Fusion, eMDs Solutions, and Greenway Prime Suite.

EHR Business Intern, Loma Linda University - Loma Linda, CA

March 2020 - June 2020

Loma Linda University Health Informatics Department provides interns with an overview of information services including EPIC (EHR Platform)

Hands on training from Electronic Health Record Specialists, shadowing, and mentorship

EDUCATION & CREDENTIAL

- Certificate, Software Engineering, Flatiron Remote, CA (December 2021)
- Coursework: Ruby on Rails, JavaScript
- MS, Health Informatics, Loma Linda University Loma Linda, CA (June 2020) GPA: 3.9
- Coursework: System Design, Health Information Technology, Data Management, Biostatistics
- BA, Psychology, California State University, Fullerton Fullerton, CA (February 2015)
- Lean Six Sigma Green Belt Certification, Loma Linda University Loma Linda, CA (December 2019)

Beyond Technical

Project Management, Customer Service

U.S. Citizen

References will be provided upon request